# **Devante Gandy**

Software Enginer

devantegandyse@gmail.com • +17165209019

https://www.linkedin.com/in/devantegandy/ • https://dev4ntegandy.github.io/portfolio/

#### **Summary**

A talented software developer with a strong passion for software development & engineering. Experience designing, developing, and troubleshooting complex solutions throughout the entire software development life cycle. A motivated self-learner who enjoys exploring and implementing new and emerging technologies.

#### Skills

JavaScript • HTML/CSS • C# • .NET Framework • React • Git • Azure • Microsoft SQL Server

## **Work Experience**

#### **Full-Stack Web Developer**

Sep 2021 - Feb 2023 • 1 yr 5 mos

Entropy • Full-time

Remote

#### Technologies: Adobe Experience Manager • JavaScript • HTML/CSS

As a web application developer with Entropy Multimedia, I had the opportunity to use industry leading content management solutions such as Adobe Experience Manager along with the power of cutting-edge hosting environments such as the Amazon Cloud to architect systems that allow both technical and non-technical users to create and maintain dynamic web sites that scale.

### Jr. Software Engineer

Feb 2023 – present

HOSPITALITY FURNISHINGS & DESIGN, INC. • Full-time

Remote

#### Technologies: JavaScript • HTML/CSS • C# • .NET Framework • Microsoft SQL Server

- Developed and maintained high level features that lead to improved functionality throughout the company
- Set the company standard for building grids using Kendo Grid and custom features that improved the speed throughout each module.
- Lead the Redesign and Redevelopmentproject for the "Vendor Portal" leading to a widespread speed improvment and overall a better workflow.
- Lead the Redesign and Redevelopment project for the "Blades" which helped Sales Reps speed up their workflow and produce more information at a glance.

## **Software Engineer Fellow**

Mar 2021 - Jun 2021 • 3 mos

General Assembly • Internship

Remote

### Technologies: Python • JavaScript • HTML/CSS • Django • React

Experience with the latest front- and back-end programming languages, tools, and methodologies. Worked with Figma to design and build user applications and iterations based on user feedback. Object-oriented programming conceptsIncorporating functionality from third-party APIsAdding complexity with Python, Django, and more. Selected appropriate libraries and open source technologies for project integration. Developed new products and added new functionality to existing software systems.

## **Projects**

## **Azimuth Real Estate Group**

Dec 2022 - Dec 2022 •

Technologies: JavaScript • HTML/CSS • Next.js • React

Developed using NextJS & ReactJS Features an advanced property filtering system, property details page with an image carousel, separate routes for Buying and selling properties.

Portfolio Dec 2024 – present

Technologies: HTML/CSS • JavaScript

A Simple Responsive portfolio using HTML/CSS & A little bit of Javascript

#### **Education**

# **Certification: Software Engineering**

Mar 2021 - Jun 2021 • 3 mos

**General Assembly** 

Full stack & full time software engineering boot camp. Worked with latest front and back-end programming languages, tools, and methodologies. Worked with groups in order to complete projects and assignments. Worked with Github while communicating accurately.

#### **Certifications & Awards**

Software Engineering Immersive - General Assembly

Jun 2021

Azure Data Fundamentals - Microsoft Feb 2024